# SERHII NAHORNYKH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



063-310-38-92



serg.extazy@gmail.com



Ukraine, Uman



nagornykh.me

## PROFILE

I am front-end developer with over 5 years of experience, specializing in React and Vue. Worked in various domains, such as Customer Feedback, Fintech, and Advertising. Inspired by the development of modern front-end technologies, I try use contemporary approaches and best practices to create interactive applications.

## SKILLS

- Vue, React, Nuxt
- Javascript/Typescript
- GraphQL, Rest api, Websocket
- · Vite, Webpack, Gulp
- Vuex, Pinia, Apollo Client
- Sass, PostCss, TailwindCss
- Vue Test Utils, Vitest
- Eslint, Prettier, Stylelint

## EXPERIENCE

#### FRONT-END DEV

Echoes.io - NYC startup

2022 - 2023

- Migrate codebase tech stack to Vue3
- Participate in developing front-end part of microservice
- Develop new features and connected them to GraphQL API
- · Refactor old code base
- Implement error tracking for SPA with Vue sentry
- Participate in code-review session

### FRONT-END DEV

Avra Technology - it product company

2017 - 2021

- Develop dashboard, statystic page with charts
- Develop new features and connect it to rest api
- Develop Vue.js UI library for internal products and integrate it into CRM platform
- Integrate AgGrid for display table data
- Increase rendering performance
- Write technical documentation for UI library
- Redesign products, implement UI templates for customization CRM appearance from admin panel

## EDUCATION

## CHERKASY STATE TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY

Master of Computer System and Networks

2012 - 2016

#### CHERKASY STATE BUSINESS-COLLEGE

Bachelor's degree in Computer Systems and Networks

2008 - 2012